

Romila Vlad Alexandru

 P Iași, Iași, România
 L +40757781970
 ➤ romilavlad2001@gmail.com

Summary

I am a React-Native developer, with past experience using back-end technologies too. I have released numerous mobile apps for both Android and iOS. When asked to describe me, colleagues say that I am a fast learner and a productive developer. I strive to have my code as clean as possible and always assume responsibility for it. My current favourite hobby is home-automation, loving to modify all my smart gadgets.

Experience

WEB DEVELOPER, HOGARTH WORLDWIDE, DECEMBER 2018-AUGUST 2019

- Being a Junior, I worked on simple web-page editing tasks
- Created/edited web-pages ads
- Learned to be part of a team full of developers at the start of their programming journey

REACT-NATIVE DEVELOPER, DSOFT, JUNE 2019-AUGUST 2020

- Developed the company's first hybrid mobile app, making them switch from developing separate Java and Swift applications to using react-native only.
- Worked with back-end technologies like Laravel
- Released 4 apps on both App Store and Google Play Market, so I am very familiar with their app validation process

FULL STACK DEVELOPER, LOGARITHMIC SOLUTIONS, SEPTEMER 2020-PRESENT

- Worked with complex marketing automation platforms like Eloqua, Marketo, HubSpot
- Worked in the development team on marketing campaigns for clients like HP, Intel
- Developed automation scripts for the Eloqua Bulk API
- Project coordinator for the company's website remake

Education

- The National College of Iași, 2012-2016
- Computer Science High-School "Grigore Moisil" Iași, 2016-2020
- Faculty of Computer Science, "Alexandru Ioan Cuza" University, Iași, 2020-2023

Skills

- Back-end: NodeJS, ExpressJS, Flask, Python, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Laravel
- Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ReactJS, NextJS, TypeScript,
- Mobile Development: React-Native (Vanilla, Expo or ExpoKit projects), App deployment (App Store and Google Play Market)